Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is caramel chocolate cheesecake.
Let me show you how to make it. So, this
is a caramel cheesecake base. So, we're
using a salted caramel protein shake.
Feel free to use any brand you want. And
then we're going to add some sweetener,
salt, and cheesecake jell-o pudding mix.
Then, you can just blend that all
together. Throw it in the freezer for at
least 16 hours. Once it's completely
frozen, you can take it out and run it
under hot water for about a minute and
throw it in your Ninja Creamy on the
light ice cream setting. It's probably
going to come out a little bit powdery.
If it's super powdery, re-pin it and
then scrape down the sides and add your
mixing. Mine looked like it was almost
done, so I just scraped on the sides
right after that first spin. Made a hole
in the middle and added my Oreos and
then ran on the mixing setting. Now,
while that is spinning, we can get our
cheesecake bites prepped. I just used
this store brand generic cheesecake. And
I chopped it into these little cubes and
then coated them in some graham cracker
crumbs. So, you might be able to find
some better cheesecake bites, but use
whatever you can find and throw them on
top and you're good to